<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patch-notes on Barnard&#39;s Star</title>
    <link>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patch-notes on Barnard&#39;s Star</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 12:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bstar.app/patch-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>18c Patch Notes - Balance Changes &amp; Bugfixes</title>
      <link>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/18c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/18c/</guid>
      <description>Another small update - but some big balance changes coming in!
Balance Changes Lurker and newly updated Acid Junkie have enjoyed a month of considerable influence. In general, the crazy plays Lurker&amp;rsquo;s Burrow and Junkie&amp;rsquo;s Acid Dash enable are so powerful as to be meta-altering &amp;ndash; that is, they&amp;rsquo;re so strong, any team not including them is at a disadvantage. After discussion in Discord, I&amp;rsquo;ve opted for some strong nerfs. These should preserve their gameplay identity and allow interesting plays, while removing the most problematic combos</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18b Patch Notes - Bugfixes</title>
      <link>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/18b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/18b/</guid>
      <description>This is a minor bugfix update - please see the last patch notes for the meaty Season 3 changes!
Note also that this patch doesn&amp;rsquo;t fix all the known bugs, either. There are several outstanding bugs that will be fixed in a later update.
Bugfixes Fixed: Some UI graphics looked quite bad due to an increased compression level. Fixed: A burrow covered by oil would sometimes render behind the oil, instead of in front of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18a Patch Notes - 3-4 Player Games, and Beginning of Season 3</title>
      <link>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/18a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 22:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/18a/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to version 18a! The big feature this version adds to the game is the ability to have 3-4 player games, instead of just 2 players.
This version also kicks off Season 3, with 3 new fighters (one per faction), some new 4-player maps, and tons of balance changes!
This is a very large update and has taken a long time to develop. Thanks for your patience!
3-4 Player Games So far, every game in Barnard&amp;rsquo;s Star has been limited to exactly 2 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17d Patch Notes - Friends system</title>
      <link>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/17d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 13:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/17d/</guid>
      <description>This patch adds a new Friends system! Add other players as friends, and invite them to games, directly from the app. It also adds the ability to choose an icon for your profile, and fixes several bugs from previous updates.
Profile icon Customize your profile by choosing an icon from your badges, and the fighters you&amp;rsquo;ve unlocked:
Use the pencil icon in the top right of your profile to change which icon is being displayed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17b Patch Notes</title>
      <link>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/17b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 14:05:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/17b/</guid>
      <description>This patch mainly consists of bugfixes relating to changes made in the last patch, 17a (the one that introduced the beginning of season 2). Here&amp;rsquo;s a big ol&amp;rsquo; list of &amp;rsquo;em.
Bugfixes When an ability shoves a fighter into cover, it didn&amp;rsquo;t deal damage to the cover. Now it does. For the purposes of unlocking Catalyst, &amp;ldquo;electrify&amp;rdquo; wouldn&amp;rsquo;t count as stun. Now it does. Fixed a bug where shooting an acid bubble created a smokescreen tile instead of an acid tile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17a Patch Notes - Beginning of Season 2</title>
      <link>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/17a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 11:29:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstar.app/patch-notes/17a/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to version 17a, the very first balance patch since Barnard&amp;rsquo;s Star was launched!
(Geez, about time, you might be thinking!)
Due to the way Barnard&amp;rsquo;s Star was designed and coded, the game logic has to stay deterministic in order to be correctly simulated on both client and server. This means that client and server need to be updated in lockstep with each other. But due to the iOS App Store and the Google Play Store requiring a review of each app version before they&amp;rsquo;re released, we don&amp;rsquo;t really have exact control over when updates are released.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
